Jordan Tyson.
>> Jordan, what's good, bro?
>> What's up, man?
>> I just talked to your uh after you got
drafted, I talked to your new wide
receivers's coach, uh Keith Williams. He
said, "We got a baller." So, uh talk to
us a little bit about uh what you what
you were feeling when you're going
through uh when you're walking down that
tunnel and you showed all those
emotions.
>> Yeah, it was it was kind of like my
first time by myself. was with the
family, felt the warmth of them. And
then when I got into the tunnel, I kind
of just felt the warmth of the Lord. He
was just I just felt his presence. I was
just being so gracious in the moment. I
just had to get on one knee, say the
prayer that I always say. I thank the
Lord for everything spiritual, mental,
and physical in my life. It's because of
you I'm able. Had to get on the knee and
say it. And I had to finish my walk to
the tunnel, got to the mirror. I was
crying like a little baby, but yeah, we
good.
>> Uh Jordan right here in the middle. Uh
what message of hope do you hope to
share with young athletes that are going
to look up to you or look up to you now?
>> Yeah, just be who you say you want to
be. If you want to be a great player, if
you want to go to the NFL, it takes a
lot of work ethic. Um takes a lot of
sacrifice. So just be who you say you
want to be and your actions should line
the accord.
>> Hey Jordan, uh what is the uh New
Orleans community getting in a player
like you?
>> Yeah, they they going to give my all. I
promise I love football too much to
disrespect the game. I'm I'mma work my
tail off. I'm not going to cheat
anybody. I'm going to do everything the
right way and yeah, they going they
going to give my all.
>> Hey Jordan, first of all,
congratulations, man. So happy for you.
Second of all, from the moment that I
got to Pittsburgh, you've just it's been
radiating off of you, man. Your faith um
you took the media room to church in a
sense in the biggest moment of your
life, bro. How does it feel to just wear
your faith on your sleeve um in this
moment?
>> Yeah, it's because of him I'm able um I
shouldn't boast in myself, but boast in
the Lord even more that I'm able to sit
in this chair and be be an NFL player.
So it's it's not it's not by my
strength, it's by his. So I just
continue to give him the glory and
that's what we're called to do.
>> Jordan Christian Oliver Seat and Hall
Center for Sports Media. U first things
first, congratulations. Your faith is
really admirable. So God bless you. Um
my question, you versus your brother
Jaylen to 11. Who wins? I got to ask.
[laughter]
>> He he gonna win, but I'm I'mma be close.
I'm'll be close. I'll probably get like
six or seven.
Hey Jordan, Ashley Holder in Cleveland.
Um Jaylen dropped 13 tonight in the Cavs
game three.
>> Did they lose? Did they end up losing?
>> They did lose. So that's why I couldn't
really finish that one. The positivity.
But what has Jaylen been able to teach
you about being a pro?
>> Yeah, he's he's been the whole blueprint
to be honest. Even from high school to
college and NIL and now to the pros,
he's he's been the blueprint for me. He
showed me the way. He paved the path and
I kind of just um follow his every move
and kind of correlate it to my sport. So
yeah, he's he's been everything to me.
Instilled work ethic in me at a young
age and wouldn't be here without him for
sure.
>> Hey Jordan Don with Roundtable Sports. I
just wanted to ask what are your top
five wide receivers currently in the NFL
right now?
>> Um Justin Jeffson, Jamar Chase,
um Puka Nua JSN,
and there's a lot of people that can go
at five. Um,
Chrysavi.
>> Hi Jordan. Congratulations. Um, I know
you spoke a little bit about walking
through the tunnel and the emotion that
came over you. Could you speak a little
bit about once you got to that stage and
you got to see the commissioner and
share that moment that you've dreamt of
for so long, that handshake, that, you
know, dapping him up. What was that
like? Yeah, to be honest, it was seeing
all the people like seeing like how much
people really love football and seeing
the impact us football players really
have on people and um it kind of it's
kind of like motivation. It keeps me
going like it wants me to be the best
player I possibly can be. So, I think I
think the people is the special part
just seeing seeing all them people.
>> Jordan, how does your game complement
Chris Olive?
>> Yeah. Um I think we both can do a lot on
the field. We both can do um anything
and everything at the receiver position,
but now we can just take pressure off
each other. So, he can't get two people
on him. We They got to leave us
one-on-one at some point. So, I feel
like we going we going to do good in
them one-on-one matchups.
>> Jordan, you're joining a young offense
led by Tyler Shuck and Chris Ave. Walk
us through your thought process as you
join them and attempt to establish the
Saints as a premier offense in the
league.
>> Yeah. Um yeah, we also got a new running
back in Travis TN. Um that's that's
going to be really cool. But um yeah, I
think we got all the right pieces in the
building to to at least win our division
and hopefully go even farther in the
playoffs and win the Super Bowl. But um
I think
I think we're going to be just fine. I
think Kell Moore has a plan in his
offense. He he knows what he's doing.
He's done it for a long time and I think
it's going to be all right.
>> Jordan, Arizona State has been putting
right here. Arizona State has been
putting a lot of guys in the league uh
recently. What does it mean to just be
able to add to that and put Arizona
State on the map?
>> Yeah. Um, Dilly, when I first got there,
it was always activate the valley, text
the Tempi. Those were our two slogans.
And um, feel like we're just doing it
just doing our part in activating the
valley. Um, making people want to come
to ASU, making people um, want to come
to Tempe. And um, yeah, I feel like
there's definitely a it's a place you
can be successful. So, I feel like you
have the right building people in the
building in terms of Hines Ward in the
receiver room and then Kenny Dillingham
just always being so real and honest
with his players and yeah, they they
have a a great formula going over there
and is going to continue to push other
NFL players out as well.
>> Two more.
>> How you doing over here? Thomas Long,
Disability Channel. Uh, just want to ask
you going out there uh in the NFL, who
is the one defense that you don't want
to go up against? Anybody out there that
you fear at all? I wouldn't say fear,
but there's definitely a lot of tricky
defenses. You got Spagnolia and the
Chiefs. He has a very tricky defense.
Tampa Bay, they blitz a lot. So, um,
yeah, definitely some tricky ones. Gonna
have to watch a lot more film and take
notes and stuff like that. So, yeah, I'm
I'm going to be ready though.
>> Last one.
>> You have an opportunity to bring back
alive a great receiver.
What knowledge have you taken from
somebody like John Jefferson?
John Jefferson,
>> star receiver for Arizona State.
>> John Jefferson.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, John Jefferson. Oh, I know exactly
what you talking about, mother.
[laughter]
>> Okay. Okay.
>> He be he comes to every game still to
this day. Um he he always talk. He was
like, um, how great do you want to be?
That's what he always says. So, yeah,
that's that's that's my boy. We always
talk before every game. And yeah,
>> what James Loftton said, that's the only
receiver he ever knew that practiced how
to uh catch a dive and catch every g uh
every day at practice.
>> Thank you guys.